scrum.org 2016-03-15

# Privacy Policy | Scrum.org - The home of Scrum

_Last Modified: September 19, 2011_

#### **Personally Identifying Information**

When you register for certain Scrum.org products or services, we will ask you to provide your name and contact information. If you purchase any of our products or services, we also collect your payment information. The information we collect may be combined with information obtained from other Scrum.org services and other companies. We may use cookies and other technologies to keep track of your interactions with our sites and services.

#### **How We Use Information**

We use personal information to communicate with you, provide you with services, and to help us improve our products and services. We list the first and last names of customers that have passed our assessments and become certified on our website. We do not sell, rent, or lease our customers' information to third parties. In order to help provide our services, we sometimes must provide information to our partners and other companies that work on our behalf. Cookies are used to offer a personalized experience, or to improve our sites and services. We do not conduct phone or postal marketing.

#### **Your Privacy Choices**

  * You may review and correct your personal information and preferences
  * You may choose to have your name removed from the certification list on our website at anytime
  * You may opt-out of emails from us
  * You may turn off cookies in your browser

#### **How to reach us**

If you have additional questions about our privacy policy, or how we use personally identifiable information, please email us at [privacy@scrum.org](mailto:privacy@scrum.org).
